■
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
翻译：红豆包      IZ      小糯
■
校对：小糯      时间轴：今
后期：加森      总监：小糯
■
《开心汉堡店》
第三季第二集
■
鲍鲍
So, Bobby,
我好期待你和琳达能够参加
I can't wait to see you and Linda
今晚的万圣节派对
at my Halloween party tonight.
我今年花了不少心思呢
I went all out this year.
我今晚要带孩子们玩"不给糖就捣乱"  泰迪
Uh, actually, I'm taking the kids trick-or-treating tonight, Teddy.
所以可能去不了了
So, I probably can't make it.
可你给我的答复是
Oh. I noticed here that you, uh,
"也许吧"
RSVP'd online and you clicked "Maybe."
是没错  可这"也许"的可能性不太大
Right. Uh, that was kind of a soft <i>Maybe</i>.
"也许"就是"也许"  鲍勃  不是
<i>Maybe</i> means <i>Maybe</i>, Bob. It doesn't mean
"我不好意思直接拒绝"
"I'm too scared to say no."
我收到42条"也许吧"  鲍勃
Uh, uh... I got 42 <i>Maybes</i>, Bob!
这谁能想到啊
Who can plan for that?
我的宝贝们回来了
There's my little candy corns.
忧郁金刚狼  好吓人  好忧郁
Ooh. Sad Wolverine. Scary and sad.
我是剪刀手爱德华  老妈
I'm Edward Scissor Hands, mom.
你整晚拿着剪刀乱跑可不太好  露易丝
Uh, I'm not sure about you walking around with scissors all night, Louise.
要不你扮成汤匙手爱德华怎么样
Why don't you be Edward Spoon Hands?
别傻了  今天是万圣节  不是胆小鬼节
Get real. It's Halloween. Not Hallowuss.
蒂娜扮的是木乃伊  好性感哦
And Tina's a Mummy. Sexy.
去年我扮的是妈妈
Last year I was a Mommy.
今年我扮的是木乃伊妈妈
This year I'm a Mommy Mummy.
我是单身妈妈  身兼两职
And I'm single and I'm working two jobs,
正在努力恢复正常生活
and I'm just trying to get back out there.
蒂娜  你明天得把这身装束缠回纸筒上
Tina, you have to put your costume back on the roll tomorrow.
-别给我浪费纸  -好
- I'm not losing that much TP. - Okay.
吉恩看起来也很棒
Oh, and Gene looks great, too.
等等  你扮的是什么  宝贝
Wait, what are you, hon?
说唱歌手兼女演员  奎因・拉蒂法
I'm rapper/ actress Queen Latifah
造型来自她的单曲"一心一意"
from her U.N.I.T.Y. phase.
主题鲜明  充满政治寓意  我喜欢
Oh, God, so specific and political. I love it.
由于不满男性主宰打击乐
她为自己取名奎因・拉蒂法[优雅女王]
好了孩子们  收拾收拾关店
All right, kids, help me close up shop
然后我们都去参加"不给糖就捣乱"
and we can all go trick-or-treating.
老爸  今年我们想要自己去玩
Dad, we've decided that this year we'd like to go trick-or-treating alone.
-自己去  -我们独自降生  独自逝去
- Alone? - We're born alone, we die alone,
活着时  我们也要独自"不给糖就捣乱"
and in between, we trick or treat alone.
可是你们喜欢和我一起玩啊
But you kids love trick-or-treating with me.
这才是意义所在
That's the best part.
对  这才是意义所在
Yeah, that's the best part.
"对  这才是意义所在"
"Yeah, that's the best part."
闭嘴  闭嘴
Shush, shush.
我说不好  今天  今天是万圣节
I, I don't know. I mean, it's, it's Halloween.
外面会有点危险
You know, things can get a little weird out there.
让他们自己去玩吧  鲍鲍  好啦
Oh, just let them go, Bobby. Come on.
好吧
Fine.
你们今年可以自己去玩"不给糖就捣乱"
You can trick or treat by yourselves this year.
但是要走往年的那条路线
But you stick to our regular route
并且要在九点之前回家
and I want you home by 9:00.
太好了  你们可以来参加我的派对了
Hooray! You can come to my party.
对哦  太好了
Oh, right, great.
今年万圣节我要嗑糖嗑到不省人事
I want this to be the sugar high I never come down from.
拿一块吧
好吧  出师不利  出师不利
Okay, bad start. Bad start.
去下一家
Let's keep moving.
不给糖就捣乱
Trick or treat.
这有一些牡蛎饼干
Uh, here's some oyster crackers.
赶紧走吧
Now get out of here.
不给糖就捣乱
Trick or treat.
今天是万圣节吗
Is it Halloween?
给  这是我们店的排队号
Here, uh, take some deli numbers.
明天你们可以抢先购买熟食
You'll be the first in line tomorrow.
不给糖就捣乱
Trick or treat.
这些好吃的海藻糖
Some delicious seaweed candy
是我独自去新加坡旅游带回来的
from my solo vacation in Singapore.
我要了  查尔斯・狄更斯
Wrap it up, Charles Dickens.
你又不是按照说话字数挣钱的
You're not being paid by the word.
-鲍鲍  琳达  -你好  泰迪
- Bobby. Linda. - Oh! Hi, Teddy.
欢迎参加我的"黑橙派对"
Welcome to my Black & Orange Party.
泰迪  你还真是花了不少心思
Teddy, you really went all out.
我今早把所有东西都喷了遍漆
I spray-painted everything this morning.
是啊  有点呛人
Yeah, it's uh, a little strong.
开扇窗户吧
Maybe we should open a window or something.
我倒是想
Yeah, I would,
可是窗户刷完漆都打不开了
but they're painted shut.
来个煮鸡蛋吧
Can I offer you a hard-boiled egg?
我用记号笔把它们都涂成了黑橙色
I colored them black and orange with a marker.
那是什么呀
What was that?
大家不必惊慌
No need to be scared, everybody.
那是我养的豚鼠  弗兰西斯
Just my guinea pig, Francis.
你们可以叫她弗兰奇
You can call her Frankie.
但千万别叫她弗兰  她讨厌被这么叫
But just don't call her Fran. She hates that.
叫弗兰西内裤怎么样
What about Francy Pants?
圣人弗兰西斯的内裤
Saint Francis' pants, huh?
-你脑子进水了吗  -怎么了
- What's wrong with you? - What?
你没穿角色服  鲍勃
Hey, you're not wearing a costume, Bob.
我压根也没想穿
I just didn't think I needed to wear a costume.
又不是小孩子
It's not a kids party.
所有人请注意
Hey, everybody,
-这里有人坏了规矩  -你要干嘛
- we've got a party violation over here. - What are you doing?
鲍勃没穿角色服
Bob is not wearing a costume.
邮递员Mike也没穿啊
Mike the mailman's not wearing a costume.
Mike扮的是小兔子
Mike's a bunny.
-那不是兔子  -我是兔子
- He's not a bunny. - I'm a bunny.
你安了个棉花球
You have a cotton ball.
-他安了个棉花球  -在你的制服上
- He has a cotton ball. - On your uniform.
想法很好
It's a great idea.
我带你去换身衣服吧
Now we're gonna get you to the costume closet.
-类似楚巴卡的角色服  -不要
- We got some sort of Chewbacca. - No.
-太阳  -不要
- The sun. - No.
-夏日科学怪人  -坚决不要
- Summer Frankenstein. - That's not a thing.
-这件最适合你了  -不不不
- I think we got a winner here. - No, no, no.
你看  好多了吧
There, all better.
你现在看起来没那么二了
Now, you don't look so ridiculous.
我用两包辣酱跟你换一个福饼
I'll trade you two packets of hot sauce for a fortune cookie.
再给我几块喉糖我就同意
Throw in some cough drops and you got a deal.
成交
Sold.
这座小镇一到万圣节就异常恐怖
This town is horrible at Halloween.
这是我们第一次独立捣乱
We're trick-or-treating by ourselves for the first time ever;
咱们去搞点真正的糖果
we need to get some real candy.
跟着我
Follow me.
我知道去哪找
I know where we can go.
我们去富人区
We're going where the rich people live.
有钱人的万圣节档次更高
Rich people are better at Halloween.
还有美容护理
And skin care.
所以我们要去...
That's why we're going to...
皇颅岛
King's Head Island.
我应该多缠些手纸的
Aah, I should have worn more toilet paper.
好吧  我承认这里比我想的要冷一点
Okay, uh, okay, I admit it's a little colder than I thought it would be.
我可不想死
Aah, I don't wanna die.
我没穿那条优质内裤
I'm not wearing my good underpants
我会难为情的
and I'd be so embarrassed.
好像暖和了十来度吧
Did it just get ten degrees warmer?
那只海鸥对我眨眼呢
I think that seagull just winked at me.
你好
Hello.
皇颅岛  很高兴见到你
King's Head Island, nice to meet ya.
现在开始不给糖就捣乱
Now, l trick or treat ya.
这里好干净啊
Wow, look how clean it is.
我都敢喝水坑里的水
I could drink from the puddles.
我一定要喝
I'm going to.
伙计们  不错嘛
Hey, guys. Sweet 'tumes.
打扮得不错
Costumes.
剪刀手爱德华  酷
Edward Scissor Hands, cool.
奎因・拉蒂法  也很酷
Queen Latifah, also cool.
可算遇到知音了
Finally, somebody gets it.
手纸装  简直酷毙了
Toilet paper roll. Nailed it.
人家是木乃伊
Mummy.
-我是麦洛  -我是奈德
- Hey, I'm Milo. - I'm Ned.
那些都是糖吗
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, is that all candy?
是啊  我们已经拿回家一袋了
Yeah, we already dropped one bag off at home.
现在我们要去斯宾塞大街
Now, we're gonna head down Spencer Street.
那边都是高级住宅
That's where all the good houses are.
真是太凑巧了
Funny coincidence.
我们也要去斯宾塞大街呢
We were also gonna go down Spencer Street.
太好了
Well, great.
我要像女王一样吃糖
I'm gonna eat like a Queen.
琳  泰迪去厕所了
Come on, Lin, Teddy went to the bathroom.
机会来了  我们赶紧溜吧
Now's our chance. Let's sneak out of here.
可是你看起来好可爱啊
But you look so cute.
我好想把蛋糕从你嘴里扇出来
I wanna spank the cake right out of your face.
-不要  -来嘛
- Uh, no. - Come on.
天哪  天哪
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
有人踩死了弗兰西斯
Somebody stepped on Francis.
天哪  天哪
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
她不喘气了  她不喘气了
She's not breathing. She's not breathing.
活过来  该死  活过来
Live, damn it, live.
泰迪  让我来
Teddy, let me try.
我肺活量很大的
I have good lungs.
快来人救救她
Somebody do something.
Mike  救救她
Mike, do something.
你要我做什么  我只是个邮递员
What do you want me to do? I'm a mailman.
Mike是个邮递员
Aah, Mike's a mailman!
天哪
Oh, God.
快  动动你的小腿  弗兰西斯
Come on, move those legs, Francis.
动动你的小腿
Move those legs.
我看到了  我看到它动了
Oh, I saw it. I saw it move.
-她还活着  -不要死啊
- She's alive. - Come on.
不  她死了
Oh, no, she's dead.
No, she's dead.
有人踩死了弗兰西斯
Somebody stepped on Francis.
却什么都没做  什么都没做
And then did nothing. Nothing!
泰迪  你怎么知道她是被踩死的
Teddy, how do you know someone stepped on her?
豚鼠不是扁的
Guinea pigs aren't flat,
它们本来可不是这样的
they don't just look like this in the wild.
好吧  我们要走了
All right, well, uh, we're gonna go.
琳  拿上你的东西
Uh, Lin, get your stuff.
-好  好  好  -派对很好玩
- Yup, yup, yup. - Great party.
说真的  我希望  弗兰西斯能够...
Seriously, I hope that, uh, Francis comes...
好起来
is... gets better.
不行  不许走
Oh, no, you don't.
-干嘛干嘛  -谁也不许走
- What? What? - Nobody's leaving.
杀手就在这间屋子里
The killer is inside this room.
谁也不许走  直到我找到那个男人
No one leaves until I find him.
或是女人
or her.
抱歉我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
谁死了
Whoa, who died?
不给糖就捣乱
Trick or treat.
你们好酷啊
Oh, you kids look great.
给  给你一块  给你一块
Here ya go, one for you. Here ya are.
非洲人
Oh, Africa.
比尔又吐我浴盆里了吗
Hey, is Bill puking in my bidet again?
一整块
Full bars?
一整块  一整块
Full bars? Full bars!
她刚刚给了我们一块完整的巧克力
She just gave us full-sized chocolate bars.
她知道吗
Does she know?
天啊  这是意外吗
Oh, my God, was it an accident?!
刚刚发生了什么事
What just happened?
这样你们的经济都没崩溃
How does this not topple your economy?
我的三观被彻底颠覆了
Everything I knew to be true just went out the window.
瓦格纳一家正在圣巴特度假
The Wagners are on vacation in St. Bart's.
度假对他们有好处
You know what, good for them.
瓦格纳一家总是寒酸兮兮的
Those Wagners were looking run-down.
请自取一块
Please, take one.
拿两块会怎么样呢
What happens when you take two?
我被咬住了  救命
Aah, it got me. Help!
等等  根本没事嘛
Oh, wait a minute. Nothing happens.
我拿三块
I'll take three.
谢谢你们  瓦格纳
Thanks, Wagner family.
祝在教堂玩好  话说圣巴特是教堂吗
Have fun at church or whatever St. Bart's is.
我的手被咬住了  开玩笑的啦
Ah, it's got my hand. Just kidding.
露易丝演得要搞笑很多
It was funnier when Louise did it.
警官  让我说几句
Ma'am, I'm speaking now.
我让你说半天了  你也让我说几句
I let you speak. Now let me speak.
轮不到你告诉我什么时候打911
You don't tell me when to call 911.
警察不来了
The police aren't coming.
看来我得亲自调查了
Looks like I have to do this investigation myself.
泰迪  我真心觉得
Teddy, I really don't think anyone
不会有人故意杀死弗兰西斯的
at your party purposely killed Francis.
情急之下谁都有可能痛下杀手
Every man is capable of murder if he's pushed far enough.
甚至是你  鲍勃
Even you, Bob.
你整晚都在窝在角落里
You've been stewing in the corner all night.
你在说什么呢  泰迪
What are you talking about, Teddy?
你有时是挺暴躁的  鲍勃
You can get a little testy, Bob.
千万别给他买V领T恤
Don't buy him a V-neck T-shirt, whatever you do.
他会抓狂的
He goes berserk.
你也不能完全避嫌  琳达
You're not in the clear either, Linda.
你无法忍受弗兰西斯抢你风头是吧
You couldn't share the spotlight with Francis, could you?
所以你把她踩死了
You had to stomp her out.
少指控我  泰迪
Don't accuse me, Teddy.
你是她的配偶
You're the spouse.
凶手通常都是配偶
It's always the spouse.
他们杀人有瘾
Passion of murder passion.
泰迪  你越来越不靠谱了
Teddy, you're going crazy.
你的派对都被你自己毁了
I mean, you're kind of ruining your own party.
或者是被丹尼斯毁了
Or did Dennis ruin my party
因为是你杀了弗兰西斯
by killing Francis.
我才没杀你那只二逼耗子呢
I didn't kill your freaking rat.
也许你不是凶手  丹尼斯
Maybe you didn't, Dennis.
但我知道你有做色情按摩
But I know you get dirty massages.
别忘了还有邮递员Mike
And let's not forget about Mike the Mailman.
我  我怎么了
Me? What about me?
你的走路姿势  充满威胁的走路姿势
It's your walk. Your menacing walk.
踏得整个小镇砰砰直响
Slamming your feet all over town.
左脚  右脚
Left, right,
杀戮  杀戮
Kill, kill.
他是跛脚  泰迪
It's a limp, Teddy.
你明知道Mike的腿不一样长
You know Mike has uneven legs.
所以我才穿着特制的鞋
It's why I wear my special shoes.
你是说凶器吧
Don't you mean murder weapons?
我有个主意
Yeah, you know what?
我要看下每个人的潜在凶器
I actually wanna see everyone's potential murder weapons.
都把鞋放进来  马上
Yeah, shoes in the chip bowl, now.
那么好的薯条可惜了了
Aww, those were good chips.
是很可惜  琳达
Yeah, they were, Linda!
非常非常可惜
They were good chips!
好啦  伙计们
Okay, guys.
已经很晚了
It's getting pretty late.
最好赶快离开这里
Better get off the streets, huh?
我们有点贪心了
We're pushing it a little.
-你觉得呢  -没错
- Uh, don't you think? - Yeah.
什么意思  我们才刚刚开始
What do you mean? We're just getting started.
还有好多条街的糖果
There's a whole other street here full of sugar
等着激高我们的血糖值呢
just waiting to course through our veins.
地狱猎手
Hell Hunt.
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
是啊  你为什么要小声说"地狱猎手"
Yeah, why did you just whisper "Hell Hunt"?
你们不知道地狱猎手是什么吗
You guys don't know about Hell Hunt?
你们不是本地人吧
You're not from Kingshead Island, are you?
我们来自大陆本土  美国
We come from the mainland: America.
每年万圣节  在大人们都喝醉之后
Every Halloween, after all the parents get drunk,
大孩子就到处为非作歹
the teenagers come out and they go freaking crazy.
他们骑车四处乱逛  肆意破坏
They ride around town on their bikes, vandalize stuff,
如果有小孩子还在外面逗留
and if any little kids are still out,
我听说他们...我听说他们...
I heard they, uh... I heard they, uh...
我听说他们...
I heard they, uh...
-他们...  -有屁快放
- They, uh... - Say it.
我听说他们会把你剃成光头
I heard they shave your head.
我听说他们会猛砸装满尿的气球
I heard they throw balloons full of pee.
三年前  我哥哥的朋友在外面待到很晚
Three years ago my brother's friend stayed out too late
结果回家时满身都是糖浆  眉毛也没了
and he came home covered in syrup without any eyebrows.
我才不信呢
Yeah, I don't know about all this.
说什么的都有
That's a lot of different stories.
我喜欢糖浆
I like syrup.
听着  外面非常危险
Look, it's not safe.
我们必须待在家里
We've got to get indoors.
你们也最好赶回码头
And you guys need to get to the dock.
多谢提醒  麦洛
Cool tip, Milo.
走吧  我们再去要点糖果
Come on, guys. Let's go get some more candy.
-什么声音  -什么
- Huh, what was that? - Huh? What?
-你们听到了吗  -没有
- Did you hear that? - No.
地狱猎手来了  快躲起来
Hell Hunt! Hide!
小朋友  快出来玩吧
Oh, kids, come out and play.
是地狱猎手
It's Hell and Hunt!
韦德・伯格斯[美国前职棒选手]
Hey, Wade Boggs,
你喜欢蛋蛋不
do you like eggs?
尝尝这些蛋蛋味道如何
How do you like these eggs?!
不怎么样
Ow! I don't like 'em!
宝宝别哭  宝宝别哭
Please don't cry. Please don't cry.
打扰一下
Ah, quick question.
有谁知道怎么回船上吗
Does anyone here know how to get back to the ferry?
你好  阿曼达
Hey, Amanda!
你好  布莱斯  最近怎么样
Hey, Bryce. What's up?
没什么特别的
Oh, not much.
就是  跟兄弟们出来  玩玩
Just, uh, hanging out with my... budsies.
我还记得高二那年的情景
I remember when I was a sophomore.
地狱猎手的把戏有够二的
Hell Hunt's so lame.
是啊  你是想说
Yeah. I mean, it's like...
"别幼稚了"  是吧
"Grow up." Right?
不过你们还在延续这项传统也挺好的
I guess it's cool you guys are keeping up the tradition, though.
必须的  地狱猎手抛拍
Oh, totally. Yeah, Hell Hunt's the best.
你也不错
So are you.
-啥  -我是说你的车
- What? - Um, that's your car.
你在开吗  你在开这辆车吗
That you're driving? That's your car that you drive?
那位老兄快不行了
This guy is dying out there.
他只需要做自己
He just needs to be himsef.
不  他应该装成别人
Oh, no. He should pretend to be someone else.
-谁在那儿  -什么
- What the freak was that? - What?
我好像听到什么声音
I thought I heard something.
是我幻听了  我是想说
I got 20-20 hearing. Anyway,
你可以来看我的曲棍球比赛
you should cruise by my lacrosse game.
-不了  谢谢回见  -再见
- No, thanks! Bye! - Bye.
发现目标  砸死你
There's one! Geesh!
咱们走
Let's go.
-这是哪儿  -可能是个乡村俱乐部
- Where are we? - I think it's a country club.
很像一座大型高尔夫球场模型
It's like a huge miniature golf course.
这儿的风车肯定大得出奇
The windmills are gonna be enormous.
看  那儿有光
Look. I see a light.
没准那边就是码头
Maybe that's the docks!
网球场
Tennis courts?
我看他们不像在打网球
I don't think those kids are playing tennis.
或者是打球方式严重有误
Or they're playing it very wrong.
全都对得上
Ah, they all kind of fit.
就好像她被踩了好多次
Like she got stomped a couple of times.
能把鞋还给我了吗
Can I have my shoes back now?
我是这里唯一一个一腿长一腿短的人
I'm the only one here with uneven legs.
别老踩棉花  沃布斯[你个瘸子]
Quit milking that leg, Wobbles.
这不好笑  泰迪
Whoa, that's not funny, Teddy.
没关系  我就姓这个
It's okay. It's my last name.
-好吧  左边的还给你  -谢谢
-Fine, you can have your left one back! - Thank you.
也许我们应该问问弗兰西斯谁是凶手
Maybe we should ask Francis who killed her?
你在开玩笑吗  格雷琴
Are you mocking me, Gretchen?
不  我是灵媒  泰迪
No. I'm a medium, Teddy.
我可以和死去的动物对话
I can talk to dead animals.
莫特  你的假发跟你问好
Mort, your toupee says hi.
好好笑
Good joke!
她在假装我戴着假发  真好笑
She's pretending I wear a toupee. So funny.
好了  我们要走了
Okay, we're leaving now.
没准还能跟孩子们一起闹会儿
Maybe I can still catch up with the kids.
可是格雷琴正在想办法呢
But Gretchen's onto something.
琳  她那是耍酒疯
Lin, she's just drunk.
趁她没提出搭便车之前我们赶紧走
Let's go before she asks us for a ride home.
鲍鲍  等等等等
Bobby! Psst. Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
什么  怎么了
What? What is it?
-你的衣服后面有毛  鲍勃  -啥
- You have fur on the back of your costume, Bob. - What?
还有小爪子的抓痕  天呐
And tiny little scratch marks. Oh, God!
我的天  是我...
Oh, God. I ki...
是我杀了弗兰西斯
...killed Francis.
-麦洛  -看到你们真是太好了
- Psst! Milo?! - I'm so glad you guys are here.
他们随时都会朝我们扔"尿气球"
They're gonna pee-balloon us any minute now.
我们也很高兴见到你们
Oh, yeah, we're glad we're here, too.
你知道吗
So, uh yeah, you know what?
我突然想知道
Oh, this just came to mind.
你们都去哪坐船来着
How do you get to the ferry?
是这样  顺着这条路下山
Oh, ah, okay, just follow this road down the hill
在"停"的标牌那儿右转
and turn right at the stop sign.
现在快救我们出去吧
Now help us break out of here!
有人跑了
There's kids loose!
快追
Let's get 'em!
跑啊
Run!
你们有麻烦了
You're in trouble!
-知道吗  -知道
- Get it?! - Yes!
你们跑不掉的
You can't outrun number one!
我们能
Yes, we can!
三张  谢谢
Three, please.
赶紧离开这座破岛
Let's get off this godforsaken island
回到我们的小窝吧
and back to the armpit we call home.
我好想回到自己的家
I can't wait to be back in my own house,
穿上自己的睡衣  钻到放满自己臭屁的被窝
in my own pajamas, in my own Dutch Oven.
别了  破岛
So long, island!
那些孩子真是疯狂
Oh, those kids are really getting it.
我还记得地狱猎手
I remember Hell Hunt.
现在看到鸡蛋还会害怕
Still can't stand the sight of eggs.
也不吃  也不碰
Won't eat 'em, won't touch 'em.
来盘美味的鸡蛋沙拉吧
What about a nice egg salad?
不要提鸡蛋了
No more egg talk!
就说  就提鸡蛋
Yes, more egg talk!
鸡蛋
Eggs!
走吧  吉恩
Let's go, Gene!
蒂娜  走啊
Tina, come on!
可麦洛和奈德还在那儿呢  他们需要我们
But Milo and Ned are back there, and they need us.
是吗
Do they, though?
蒂娜  这不关我们的事
Tina, this isn't our fight!
你真想留在这里被"尿气球"砸吗
Do you really want to stay here and get pee-ballooned?
我可以尿在自己身上
Yeah. I can pee on myself.
我不接受嗟来之尿
I don't need any handouts.
这座小镇给了我们前所未有的美味糖果
Listen, this town gave us the best candy we've ever seen.
我们欠了人情  我们必须回去
We owe it to them to go back.
没错  现在这巧克力都有一股内疚味了
Great. Now my candy tastes like guilt!
那好吧
Aah! Fine!
我们去救麦洛和那个谁
We'll go back and save Milo and what's-his-face,
-条件是我要扇下吉恩  -非常公平
- but I get to slap Gene. - That's fair.
我宣布将你逐出拉蒂法国度
Aah! I banish you from the land of Latifah!
皇颅超市
好了  我们要做的就是潜到网球场
Okay, so all we have to do is sneak up to the tennis courts,
拿下看门的那个
take out the guy guarding the gate,
撂倒四个小青年  然后救出孩子们
fight off four teenagers and free the kids.
我走神了  再说一遍
I zoned out. Say that again.
我们来个声东击西
We just need some kind of distraction.
皇颅超市
我马上到
I'll be right there.
我先买些口香糖和卫生棉
I'm just stopping to get gum and some t-pons.
目标锁定
Distraction located.
-好了  谁想第一个来  你吗  -不要
- All right, who wants the first pee balloon? You? - No.
-你吗  -不要
- You? - No.
好了  发送
And... send.
天啊  我收到阿曼达的短信了
Hell, yeah. I just got a text from Amanda.
"快来瓦格纳家和我们一起参加泳池派对吧"
"Pool party at the Wagner house with me and the girls."
真的吗  酷毙了
What? That's awesome!
现在游泳好像有点冷
Ugh. It's kind of cold to go pool hopping.
"瓦格纳家的泳池不冷"
"The Wagner's pool is not cold."
有点奇怪  好吧  我们走
That's weird. Okay, let's go!
-那还玩地狱猎手吗  -你疯了吗
- What about Hell Hunt? - Are you crazy?
她们可是高三的
These girls are seniors.
我听说阿曼达打了脐环
I heard Amanda's got a belly button ring.
我还听说她能用屁股把樱桃梗打成结
Well, I heard she can tie a cherry stem with her butt!
我还听说她的胸罩要特别订做
I heard she has two special order bras!
这玩意就像遥控器一样
This thing is like a remote control.
我说什么他们就做什么
They'll do whatever I say.
叫他们把屁股挤在一起
Tell them to push their butts together.
给他们调成法国口音
Give them French accents.
她让我们快点
She says hurry.
还说我们着急的时候最可爱
And that we're really cute when we hurry.
去之前先把该放的屁放完
Hey, get all your farts out now before we get there.
救命  救命  救我们出去  救命
Help! Help! Let us out of here! Help!
奎因・拉蒂法  赐我力量吧
Queen Latifah, give me strength!
太感谢了  朋友们
Thanks, guys.
谢谢你们
Oh, oh, thank you.
我实在不喜欢尿  是吧  奈德
I'm not a big fan of pee, right, Ned?
我们还要赶船呢
Well, we've got a boat to catch.
等等  我还没玩够呢
Hold on. I'm not done with this yet.
这些小鬼惹错人了  惹到我们了
These teens messed with the wrong kids. Us.
"抱歉我们晚了"
"Sorry we are late."
"奶子已经就位"
"We are getting our boobs ready."
"你们先脱光下水吧"
"You boys go skinny dipping."
"我们泳池坦诚相见"
"See you soon to skinny dip."
好咧  脱裤子吧
All right, let's pop off our pants.
汤里好多胡萝卜啊
There's a lot of carrots in that stew.
太棒了  我们在裸泳耶
This is awesome! We're skinny dipping!
我敢说要是和妹子在一起感觉会更棒
It's gonna be even better with girls, I bet!
好了  我们去坐船吧
Okay, let's get to the ferry.
我们还有好多糖果呢
This candy's not gonna eat itself.
我们应该偷走他们的衣服  扔到海里
We should steal their clothes and throw them in the ocean.
或者可以拍下照片
Or we could take pictures of them,
日后慢慢欣赏
and then later, we can look at them.
这样他们就曝光了
That would show them!
好了  我要开动了
Fine, I'm gonna get started.
巧克力  焦糖  棒棒糖  辣酱
Chocolate, caramel, lollipop, hot sauce.
好  我有主意了
Yes! That's it!
我们把辣酱挤在他们内裤上
Let's put hot sauce in their underwear!
那会有什么效果吗
Does that even do anything?
小鸡鸡最讨厌的  就是辣酱
Yeah, if there's one thing a wiener hates, it's hot sauce.
我深有感触
I learned that the hard way.
厕所玉米卷大餐
Taco on the toilet.
怎么就没人这么做呢
Why doesn't everybody do this?
11年来每天仍要温习一遍
11 years old and still learning every day.
愿你安息
And that's amazing grace.
谁还想给弗兰西斯致敬  Mike
Who would like to pay tribute to Francis? Mike?
我每次给泰迪送信
Every time I delivered mail to Teddy,
弗兰西斯都会...
Francis greeted me with a friendly...
这样欢迎我
Something like that.
怎么办  泰迪会因为我杀了弗兰西斯而杀了我的
What do I do? Teddy's gonna kill me for killing Francis.
你必须告诉他
You got to tell him.
豚鼠  是啥
A guinea pig. What is it?
不重要  我是丹尼斯
Anyway, I'm Dennis.
谢谢你们  你们真好
Thank you guys. That was beautiful.
鲍勃  你想说点什么吗
Bob, do you want to say anything?
好的  弗兰西斯是一只伟大的动物
Yes. Uh, Francis was a great animal.
她淡看人间世事
She went through her life with such poise...
我做不到  泰迪  是我杀了弗兰西斯
I can't do this. Teddy, I killed Francis.
-什么  -我当时都没注意到
- What?! - I didn't even know I did it!
我穿着这身傻路根衣本感觉不到她在下面
I couldn't feel her underneath this stupid fat suit
都是你逼我穿的
that you made me wear!
我去
Oh! Oh, God.
该死
Damn it.
你这个自作孽不可活的混蛋
You could have been Summer Frankenstein.
夏日科学怪人都没你狠毒
Summer Frankenstein wasn't good enough for you.
我真的很抱歉  泰迪
I'm really sorry, Teddy.
她陪我度过了人生中最美好的14年
She gave me the best 14 years of my life.
等下  她有14岁了吗
Wait. She was 14 years old?
它们通常能活多久
How long do they usually live?
不知道  三到五年吧
I don't know. Three to five years.
按豚鼠的时间来算  她都154岁了
Uh, she was 154 in guinea pig years.
或许你不该把她染成黑橙色的 朋友
Uh, you probably shouldn't have painted her black and orange, man.
是啊  她当时就迷糊了
Yeah, she got real dizzy.
一直在啃自己的爪子
She kept trying to eat her paw.
等等  你为什么要给豚鼠染色  泰迪
Wait. Why would you spray-paint your guinea pig, Teddy?
为了派对啊  这样才跟主题相配嘛
For the party, 'cause it went with everything.
我知道  琳  这我知道
I know... Lin, I know that.
可是泰迪  你干嘛非要这样做
But why, Teddy, would you do that?
你这问题真白痴
It's pretty stupid.
我被派对搞昏了头
I got caught up in the party.
好吧  鲍勃  是我们一起杀死了她
Okay, Bob. We both killed her.
扯平了
Fair enough.
现在我可以养白鼬了
Well, now I can get a ferret.
无论如何  感谢大家的光临
Anyway, thanks for coming, everybody.
很抱歉我说你们是杀人凶手
Sorry I called you all murderers.
如果谁想复刻这个幽灵音效
If anyone wants me to burn them a copy of this spooky sounds CD,
尽管开口就是
just let me know.
她们不会来了  我都快泡软了
They're not coming. I'm getting pruney.
我们出去吧
Let's get out of here.
冷静冷静  备好鸡鸡  兄弟
Chill out with your dills out, man.
别扫兴嘛  我打电话给她
Don't be lame. I'll call her.
搞什么...
What the...?
回见
Bye!
我应该只拿一块的
I should have just taken one!
这些大块巧克力太重了
Those full bars are weighing me down!
不
No!
露易丝
Louise?
你给几条内裤挤了辣酱
How many pairs of underwear did you hot sauced?
就一个人...穿了内裤
Only one of them... wore underwear!
你们死定了
Oh, you are dead!
我的宝宝
My baby!
给我过来
Come here!
我们的尿  好骚
Our pee! Ew!
就这样
And so,
地狱猎手反而...
the hell hunters become...
变成了我们的猎物
the ones who are being hell-huntered.
-说得好  -谢了  各位
- Well put. - Thanks, guys.
搞死他们
Mess 'em up!
再见  麦洛
Bye, Milo.
再见  麦洛的朋友
Bye, Milo's friend.
也许下个万圣节我们还会再来
We'll probably come back next Halloween.
不可能
No, we won't!
-会  -不会
- Yes! - No!
真恶心  你们看到我的手机了吗
Ooh. Gross. Have you guys seen my phone?
是被一群小屁孩...
Geesh! Uh, actually some kid... Ow!
-我被打...  -算了  再见
- I'm getting hit with... - Ugh, forget it. Bye.
就差一点
Ooh, so close!
不公平
Ugh! No fair.
我的大块巧克力都丢了
I lost all my full bars.
你可以舔我的包装纸
You can lick my wrappers.
或者吃你的包装纸
Or I can eat your wrappers!
什么也替代不了我的宝宝
Nothing will ever replace my baby,
不过这些大块巧克力也差不多了
but these full bars are coming pretty close.
我的小蛀牙们
There's my little cavities!
第一个没有我陪的万圣节  感觉如何
Yeah, how was your first Halloween without me?
我敢说一定很无聊
Pretty boring, I bet.
你们老爸杀死了一只豚鼠
Your father killed a guinea pig!
-他把它压...  -琳
- He squashed it with... - Lin!
快给我们说说
Oh, tell us about that!
是正当防卫吗
Was it in self-defense?
它对你的女人无礼了吗
Did he disrespect your woman?
没有  我只是在它身上滚了几下
No. I just... rolled on to him.
事情是这样的
Here's what happened.
-那是一个月黑风高的夜晚  -我就知道
- It was a dark and spooky night. - I knew it!